A Guide to the Colonial Papers, 1630-1778
Library of Virginia
- Series I: Chronological Files, 1630-1778., Extent: 8 boxes. (Box 142-149)
  - 1706
    - May 16 - Letter of C. Hedges (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 13))
    - May 17 - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 14))
    - May 30 - Letter of C. Hedges (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 15))
    - June 4 - Amendment of the Council (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 16))
    - June 10
      - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 17))
      - Proceedings of the House of Burgesses (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 18))
      - Address of Benjamin Harrison, Speaker of the House of Burgesses (See Oversized) (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 19))
    - June 19 - Note of Governor Edward Nott (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 20))
    - July 4 - Letter of Charles Hedges (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 21))
    - Aug. 1 - Letter of Charles Hedges (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 22))
    - Aug. 6 - Letter of R. Thompson (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 23))
    - Aug. 20 - Letter of James Jesson (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 24))
    - Aug. 26 - Letter of W. Churchill (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 25))
    - Oct. 12 - Letter of Matthew Kemp (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 26))
    - Oct. 17 - Order of the Council (See Oversized) (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 25a))
    - Nov. 20 - Order of the Council (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 27))
    - n.d.
      - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 28))
      - Petition of Masters of Ships on the York River (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 29))
      - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 30))
      - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 31))
      - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 32))
      - Amendments of the Council (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 33))
      - Letter of William Churchhill and Others (Box 143, Folder 17 (Item 34))
  - 1706/1707
    - Jan. 24 - Letter of Robert Spencer, 4th Earl of Sunderland (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 0))
    - Feb. 15 - Letter of Robert Spencer, 4th Earl of Sunderland (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 1))
    - Mar. 14 - Letter of Robert Spencer, 4th Earl of Sunderland (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 3))
  - 1707
    - Mar. 2 - Order of the Accomack County Court (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 2))
    - Mar. 18 - Petition of Joseph Mitchell (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 4))
    - Mar. - Letter of Armiger Wade (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 5))
    - Apr. 1 - Order of the Henrico County Court (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 6))
    - Apr. 5
      - Deed of Release of Thomas Pannell (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 7))
      - Letter of Governor Joseph Seymour (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 8))
    - Apr. 9 - Deed of Release of William Pannell (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 9))
    - Apr. 17
      - Order of Queen Anne (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 10))
      - Order of Queen Anne (Duplicate of above) (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 11 & 12))
      - Order of the General Court (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 13))
    - Apr. 19 - Petition of the Tuscarora Indians (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 14))
    - Apr. 25 - Order of the Council (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 15))
    - May 15 - Letter of William Bassett (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 16))
    - May 17 - Letter of Governor Joseph Seymour (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 17))
    - June 12 - Letter of John Walker (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 17))
    - June 18 - Deed of Francis & Mary Stone to Richard Buckner (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 19))
    - Sept. 2 - Letter of Abraham Salle (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 20))
    - Sept. 12 - Letter of Governor Joseph Seymour (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 21))
    - Oct. 24 - Letter of Prince George of Denmark (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 22))
    - Oct. 29 - Letter of Nathaniel Harrison (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 23))
    - Nov. 1 - Petition of Henry Haywood, Jr. (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 24))
    - Nov. 15 - Letter of Letter of Robert Spencer, 4th Earl of Sunderland (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 25))
    - Undated - Letter of Robert Beverly (Box 144, Folder 18 (Item 26))
  - 1707/1708
    - Jan. 16 - Letter of John Walker (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 1))
    - Jan. 25 - Order of Queen Anne (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 2))
    - Feb. 14 - Letter of Robert Spencer, 4th Earl of Sunderland (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 4))
    - Mar. 6 - Proceedings of the Charles Parish Vestry (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 5))
    - Mar. 10 - Letter of Nathaniel Blakiston (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 6))
    - Mar. 13
      - Petition of the Vestry of Charles Parish (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 7))
      - Warrant of Governor Edmund Jenings (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 8))
    - Mar. 17
      - Letter of Daniel Taylor (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 9))
      - Certificate of Bernard Coudert (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 10))
  - 1708
    - Jan. 6 - Deed between Stephen Coney, Constance Cromh, & Edward Austin (See Oversized Drawer) (Box 144, Folder 19 (No Item #))
    - Feb. 10 - Proclamation of Governor Edmund Jenings (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 10a))
    - Feb. 13 - Order of the Council (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 3))
    - Apr. 1
      - Order of Queen Anne (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 11))
      - Letter of Charles Stewart (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 12))
    - Apr. 14 - Proceedings of the Prince George County Court (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 13))
    - Apr. 15 - Letter of Nathaniel Blakiston (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 14))
    - Apr. 24 - Petition of George Walker (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 15))
    - Apr. 25 - Answer of the Governor & Council (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 16))
    - Apr. 28
      - Petition of William Tunley (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 17))
      - Petition of William Loury (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 18))
      - Petition of John Lomax (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 19))
    - June 10 - Order of the Council (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 20))
    - June 24 - Letter of Edmund Jenings (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 21))
    - Aug. 28 - Warrant of Henry Boyle (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 22))
    - Oct. 4 - Letter of Nathaniel Blakiston (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 23))
    - Oct. 28
      - Petition of Joseph John Jackman (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 24))
      - Petition of the Visitors & Governors of the College of William & Mary (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 25))
      - Petition of Henry Cary (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 27))
    - Undated - Petition of the Vestry of Charles Parish (Box 144, Folder 19 (Item 26))
  - 1708/1709
    - Jan. 5 - Letter of George Gordon (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 1))
    - Jan. 15 - Letter of George Gordon (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 2))
    - Feb. 19 - Order of Queen Anne (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 3))
    - Mar. 4 - Account of Sundry Disbursements for the use of the Brigantine Sea-Flower (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 5))
  - 1709
    - Feb. 20 - Letter of Nicholas Blakiston (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 4))
    - Mar. 8
      - Petition of William Holloway (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 36))
      - Petition of Brinoldus de Haes (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 37))
      - Petition of Richard Kendall (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 38))
      - Petition of the Owners of the Brigantine Society of Virginia (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 39))
    - Mar. 19
      - Proceedings of the Surry County Court (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 40))
      - Letter of Philip Ludwell (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 41))
    - Mar. 20 - Order of Edmund Jenings (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 42))
    - Mar. 24
      - Return of Isle of Wight County Court (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 43))
      - Letter of the Surry County Court (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 44))
    - Mar. 28 - Letter of Thomas Earl of Pembroke (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 45))
    - Apr. 6 - Letter of Edward Moseley (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 46))
    - Apr. 16 - Petition of Henry Cary (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 47))
    - Apr. 21 - Order of the Council (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 48))
    - May 7 - Account of William Robertson (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 49))
    - May 26 - Order of William Cary (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 50))
    - June 2 - Petition of Thomas Morgan, John Winton, John Magenis, & George Wood (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 51))
    - July 14 - Letter of Benjamin Harrison (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 52))
    - July 21 - Note of Edward Moseley (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 53))
    - July 29 - Letter of Thomas Keeling, Cason Moore, Robert Richman, and Henry Walston (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 54))
    - Aug. 10 - Letter of John Roberts (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 55))
    - Sept. 3 - Letter of Edmund Jenings (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 56))
    - Sept. 7 - Letter of William Churchill (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 57))
    - Sept. 10 - Letter of Robert Spencer, 4th Earl of Sunderland (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 58))
    - Oct. 27
      - Petition of Robin (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 59))
      - Order of the Council (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 60))
    - Nov. 8 - Letter of Joseph Dudley (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 61))
    - Dec. 7
      - Letter of William Wilson (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 62))
      - Letter of George Walker (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 63))
    - Dec. 8 - Letter of Henry Jenkins (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 64))
    - Dec. 15 - Reasons for Repealing the Acts passed in Virginia & Maryland relating to Ports & Towns (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 65))
    - Undated - Pass Granted to Indian Traders (Box 144, Folder 20 (Item 66))
  - 1709/1710
    - Mar. 3 - Letter of William Wison (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 1))
  - 1710
    - Feb. 12 - Letter of Robert Wise (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 11))
    - Mar. 14 - Commission of Col. Philip Ludwell (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 2))
    - Mar. 24 - Order of Queen Anne (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 19))
    - Apr. 15 - Letter of Capt. John Pye (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 3))
    - Apr. 17 - Petition of Abraham Le Mesurier (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 4))
    - Apr. 26 - Letter of Nicholas Smith (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 6))
    - Apr. 27 - Petition of Timothy Nicholson, William Breton, and John Tucker (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 7))
    - Apr. - Letter to William Swan (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 8))
    - Aug. 14 - Survey of the Jamaica Merchant (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 9))
    - Oct. 4 - Petition of Nathaniel West and William Carr (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 10))
    - Oct. 5 - Petition of Nathaniel West & William Carr (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 12))
    - Oct. 9 - List of Fees of John Powell, Sheriff of Northampton County (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 13))
    - Oct. 19 - Petition of Robert Beverley (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 19))
    - Oct. 26
      - Petition of Michael Archer (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 15))
      - Petition of Thomas Eldridge (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 16))
      - Petition of Richard Farrell (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 17))
      - Certificate of Phillip Ludwell & John Lewis (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 18))
    - Oct. 27
      - Petition of Francis Ballard (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 19))
      - Warrant of Peter Beverely (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 20))
      - Petition of Thomas Parker (Box 144, Folder 21 (Item 21))
    - Nov. 8
      - Act to Prevent the Destroying & Murthering of Bastard Children (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 1))
      - Order of the Council (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 13))
    - Nov. 9
      - Petition of Robert Beverley (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 14))
      - Address of the House of Burgesses (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 15))
    - Nov. 15 - Report of the Committee for Propositions & Grievances (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 16))
    - Nov. 16
      - Petition of Inhabitants of Charles City County (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 17))
      - Report of the Committee for Propositions & Grievances (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 18))
      - Petition of Elizabeth Harrison (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 19))
    - Nov. 17 - Report of the Committee for Propositions & Grievances (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 20))
    - Nov. 24 - Petition of Henry Cary (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 21))
    - Dec. 12 - Warrant of Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 10a))
    - Undated
      - Warrant of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 12))
      - Petition of Joseph Meredith (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 13))
      - Petition of James Wishard (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 14))
      - Petition of Henry Lawrence (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 15))
      - Report of the Committee for Propositions & Grievances (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 16))
      - Proposal for Furnishing the Governor's Palace (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 17))
      - Petition of the Pamunkey Indians (Box 144, Folder 22 (Item 18))
  - 1711
    - Jan. 5 - Letter of David Tupp (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 1))
    - Apr. 17 - Petition of Charles Bailey (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 2))
    - Apr. 20
      - Proceedings of the General Court (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 3))
      - Petition of John Boughan, et al. (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 4))
    - Apr. 21 - Petition of John Sandiford (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 5))
    - Apr. 28 - Account of Thomas Hayden (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 6))
    - May 6 - Petition of Inhabitants of Hampton (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 7))
    - June 16 - Letter of Governor Robert Hunter (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 8))
    - June 28 - Letter and Invoice of Henry Ceane (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 8a))
    - Aug. 15 - Petition of Francis Thornton (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 9))
    - Aug. 16
      - Petition of John Simmons (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 10))
      - Proclamation of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 10a))
    - Aug. 28 - Petition of Richard Wharton, et al. (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 11))
    - Aug. 30 - Orders, Commission, and Warrant of Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 12))
    - Oct. 25 - Certificate of Richard Littlepage (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 13))
    - Oct. 26
      - Letter of Farnifull Green (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 14))
      - Petition of William Thornton (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 15))
    - Nov. 2 - Petition of Harry Beverley (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 16))
    - Nov. 24 - Message of the House of Burgesses (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 17))
    - Nov. 28 - Message of the House of Burgesses (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 18))
    - Nov. - Bill for Appointing Rangers (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 19))
    - Dec. 22 - Proclamation of Queen Anne (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 20))
    - Proposals for Improving the Staple of Tobacco & Advancing the Public Credit (Box 144, Folder 23 (Item 21))
  - 1711/1712
    - Jan. 4 - Letter of John & Mary Ashlin to Joseph Ashlin (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 1))
    - Feb. 16 - Petition of the Inhabitants of Neuse River, North Carolina (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 2))
  - 1712
    - July 11 - Passport for Robert Hix, John Evans, David Crawley, Richard Jones, & Nathaniel Irby (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 3))
    - July - Bond of Robert Hix, John Evans, David Crawley, Richard Jones, & Nathaniel Urven (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 4))
    - Oct. 12 - Note of Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 5))
    - Oct. 20 - Order of Queen Anne (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 6))
    - Oct. 31 - Petition of Henry Fox & Nathaniel West (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 7))
    - Nov. 20 - Account of Henry Cary & John Tyler, Overseer of the Governor's House (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 8))
    - Dec. 6 - Order of Queen Anne (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 9))
    - Dec. 13 - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 10))
    - Dec. 22 - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 11))
    - Dec. 23 - Letter of Thomas Pollock, President of North Carolina (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 12))
    - Dec. 28 - Letter of Thomas Pollock, President of North Carolina (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 13))
    - Undated
      - Survey & Plat of Augustine Smith (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 14))
      - Amendments of the Council (Box 144, Folder 24 (Item 15))
  - 1712/1713
    - Jan. 15 - Letter of Thomas Pollock, President of North Carolina (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 1))
    - Jan. 20 - Letter of Thomas Pollock, President of North Carolina (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 2))
    - Jan. 25 - Letter of Thomas Pollock, President of North Carolina (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 3))
    - Jan. 30 - Depositions of John Dew and John Lewis (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 4))
  - 1713
    - Feb. 3 - Petition of Thomas Etheridge (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 5))
    - Feb. 15
      - Account of Peter Beverley (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 1))
      - Bond of William Ruckner & Henry Tyler (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 2))
      - Bond of James Bates & William Tinison (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 3))
      - Bond of William Row & William Gordon (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 4))
    - Feb. 24
      - Bond of James Lawrence & Thomas Godwin, Jr. (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 5))
      - Bond of John Duke & William Wright (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 6))
    - Mar. 8 - Letter of Thomas Pollock, President of North Carolina (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 6))
    - Mar. 15 - Bond of John Holloway & Joseph Walker (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 7))
    - Mar. 19 - Letter of Thomas Pollock, President of North Carolina (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 8))
    - Mar. 25 - List of Ships & Other Vessels Entered & Cleared in Accomack District (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 20))
    - Mar. 27 - Letter of Col. James Moore (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 21))
    - Mar. - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 22))
    - Apr. 10 - Recommendation of George Mason (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 23))
    - Apr. 15 - Petition of George Dabney (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 24))
    - Apr. 25 - Petition of Joseph Smith (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 25))
    - May - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 26))
    - June 5 - Order of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 27))
    - June - Petition of David Morgan (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 28))
    - July 31 - Commission of James Blair (See Oversized) (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 29))
    - Aug. 3 - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 30))
    - Sept. 6 - Petition of John Ingram (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 31))
    - Oct. - Caveat of Christopher Smith & William Cockrel (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 20a))
    - Nov. 14 - Report of the Committee Appointed to Inspect & Collect all the Laws in Force Relating to Tobacco (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 21))
    - Nov. - Speech of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 22))
    - Dec. 7 - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 32))
    - Dec. 8 - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 23))
    - Dec. 9 - Address of the House of Burgesses (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 24))
    - Dec. 13 - Speech of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 25))
    - Dec. 16 - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 26))
    - Dec. 19 - Memorandum of the Deputies from the Tuscarora Towns (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 27))
    - Address of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 28))
    - Undated
      - Bond of Andrew McClenahan (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 29))
      - Amendment to the Land Bill (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 30))
      - Dimensions of the Two Wings of Bruton Parish Church (Box 144, Folder 25 (Item 31))
  - 1713/1714
    - Bond of William Cole & John Stith (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 7))
  - 1714
    - Mar. 25
      - List of Ships entering the Accomack District (See Oversized) (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 2-3))
      - Bond of William Wright & John Moore (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 4))
      - Bond of Thomas Godwin, Jr., & Edmond Godwin (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 5))
      - Bond of Thomas Godwin, Jr., & Edmond Godwin (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 6))
    - Apr. 1 - Return of Births & Deaths for Mulberry Island Parish in Warwick County (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 8))
    - Apr. 14 - Petition of William Row (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 9))
    - Apr. 20 - Petition of George Major (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 10))
    - Aug. 2 - Petition of Henry Sanders (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 11))
    - Aug. 5 - Letter of Henry St. John, 1st Viscount Bolingbroke (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 12))
    - Sept. 24 - Petition of William Benston, Jr. (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 13))
    - Oct.
      - Petition of John Drewrey, Jr. (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 14))
      - Petition of John Waller (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 15))
      - Petition of Philip Lightfoot (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 16))
    - Dec. 17
      - Address of the Council & House of Burgesses (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 17))
      - Address of the Council & House of Burgesses (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 18))
    - Dec. 23 - Amendments of the Council (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 19))
    - Undated
      - Bond for Building a Storehouse (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 20))
      - Petition of Claude & Elizabeth Rouvierre (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 21))
      - Notice of George Luke (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 22))
      - Petition of Frederick Jones & Charles Chiswell (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 23))
      - Petition of Richard Cocke, Jr. (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 24))
      - Petition of William Douglas (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 25))
      - Petition of John Allen (Box 144, Folder 26 (Item 26))
  - 1715
    - Jan. 27 - Petition of Nicholas Salisbury (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 1))
    - Mar. 2 - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Filmed in Folder 28) (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 11))
    - Mar. 26 - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Filmed in Folder 28) (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 12))
    - Mar. 2 - Letter of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Filmed in Folder 28) (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 11))
    - Apr. 15 - Letter of Leonard Tarent (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 7))
    - Apr. - Petition of John Pleasants (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 8))
    - July 14
      - Deposition of Henry Atherton (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 9))
      - Letter of the Council of South Carolina (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 10))
    - July 19 - Proclamation of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 11))
    - July 21 - Articles of Agreement between Lieutenant Governor & Alexander Spotswood William Dandridge (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 12))
    - July 22 - Instructions of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 13))
    - July - Proclamation of Lieutenant Governor Alexander Spotswood (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 14))
    - Oct.
      - Petition of Godfrey Pole (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 15))
      - Petition of Henry Holdcraft (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 16))
    - Undated
      - Account of William Dandridge (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 17))
      - Petition of Nathaniel Harrison (Box 145, Folder 27 (Item 18))